continuing in this fashion always
cutting up the rightmost piece into
those same proportions you'll find that
1 - p + P * 1 - P plus p ^ 2 * 1 - p on
and on always adding P to the next power
* 1 - P equal 1 dividing both sides by 1
- P we get this nice
formula in this formula the universe has
offered a weird form of nonsense even
though the way that you discovered it
only makes sense for values of P between
0 and 1 the right hand side still makes
sense when you replace ke with any other
number except maybe for one for instance
plugging in -1 the equation reads 1 - 1
+ 1us one on and on forever alternating
between the two equals 12 which feels
both pretty silly and kind of like the
only thing that it could be plugging in
two the equation reads 1 + 2 + 4 + 8 on
and on to Infinity = -1